files.to 2017-08-01

# file.io - Privacy Policy

Last updated: April 4, 2017

Thank you for using file.io. We are committed to protecting your privacy and, for that reason, we have adopted this Privacy Policy to explain our data collection, use, and disclosure practices for the file.io services (including its website, and mobile and web-based applications, and any other tools, products, or services provided by humbly, LLC that link to or reference this Privacy Policy) (collectively, the “Services”). The Services are owned and operated by humbly, LLC, a Pennsylvania limited liability company(“we”, “us” or “our”). 

This Privacy Policy applies to information humbly collects through the Services, as well as other information provided to us online or offline by third parties, when we associate that information with customers or users of the Services; however, it does not apply to information collected from our employees, contractors, or vendors. It also does not apply to information that you share with third parties or is collected by third parties through the Services (including web traffic or crash analytics tools). You acknowledge and agree that humbly is not responsible for the data collection or use practices of any other Services user or third party utilized in providing the Services. 

This Privacy Policy describes, among other things: 

  * Personal and other information we collect about you;
  * How we use your information;
  * How we may share your information with third parties; and 
  * Your choices regarding the personal information we collect about you.

## Consent

By accessing or using the Services, you consent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use the Services. Information gathered through the Services may be transferred, used, and stored in the United States or in other countries where our service providers or we are located. If you use the Services, you agree to the transfer, use, and storage of your Personal Information (as defined below) in those countries. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. You agree that all transactions relating to the Services or file.io are deemed to occur in the United States, where our servers are located.

## Collection of Your Personal and Other Information

When you register for a premium subscription to our Services, we collect Personal Information. By “Personal Information” we mean information that can identify an individual, such as names and email addresses.

Certain aspects of the Services may also access certain features of your mobile device, including its camera and camera roll, and collect files from those features, such as photographs, videos, and other files you choose to upload using the Services. You consent to this access.

You may choose not to provide Personal Information or prevent the Services from accessing certain features of your mobile device, (subject to the controls offered by your mobile device’s operating system), but this may prevent you from receiving certain features of the Services.

We also collect non-Personal Information relating to the Services, that is, information that does not personally identify an individual. The non-Personal Information we collect includes how you interact with the Services, information generally collected or “logged” by Internet websites or Internet services when accessed or used by users, and information about your web browser or device accessing or using the Services. 

Examples of the non-Personal Information we (or our third-party service providers) may collect are:

  * Your Internet Protocol (IP address);
  * Information about your computer or mobile device, such as its maker or operating system version, 
  * The pages of our website that you viewed during a visit or thefeatures of file.io you use;
  * What information or content you view or interact with using the Services; 
  * The city and state in which you are located (but not your precise geographic location); and 
  * Unique identifiers that are not connected and cannot reasonably be connected to your identity. 

We will not use non-Personal Information to try to identify you, and if we associate any non-Personal Information with information that personally identifies you, then we will treat it as Personal Information. As discussed in more detail below, we sometimes use cookies and other automatic information gathering technologies to gather non-Personal Information. 

Information collected by the Services may be collected by us or one of our service providers acting on our behalf, but in either case, this Privacy Policy will govern the collection, use, and sharing of the information.

## Use of Your Information

We may use the information we collect to:

  * Assist us in providing, maintaining, and protecting the Services;
  * Set up, maintain, and protect accounts to use the Services;
  * Improve our online operations;
  * Process transactions;
  * Provide customer service;
  * Communicate with you, such as provide you with account- or transaction—related communications, and/or other communications relating to the Services;
  * Perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products and services and developing new products or services; and 
  * Manage and maintain the systems that provide the Services.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your Personal Information to third parties as described below. 

We may disclose Personal Information to provide the Services. We may also disclose Personal Information and non-Personal Information to companies, agents, contractors, service providers, or others engaged to perform functions on our behalf (such as processing of payments, provision of data storage, hosting of our website, conducting audits, and performing web analytics). We may license third party software to include in or use with the Services, in which case we may disclose Personal Information and/or Non-Personal Information to the licensor.

We may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties when we believe, in good faith and in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) enforce or apply the terms and conditions of the Services, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements or an enforceable governmental request, (c) protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users or other third parties, (d) prevent a crime or protect national security, or (e) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. 

Finally, we reserve the right to transfer information (including your Personal Information) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of our company relating to the Services, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, liquidation, or receivership of our business. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you of such transfer, for example via email or by posting notice on our website.

Lastly, we may also disclose non-Personal Information, aggregated with information about our other users, to our clients, business partners, merchants, advertisers, investors, potential buyers and other third parties if we deem such disclosure, in our sole discretion, to have sound business reasons or justifications. 

## Cookies and Automatic Information Gathering Technologies

Every time you use the Services (e.g., access a Service webpage), we collect non-Personal Information (discussed above in Section 2) regarding that use. For example, to improve our Services, we collect how, when, and which parts of the Services or its features you use. 

To assist us in collecting and storing this non-Personal Information, we may employ a variety of technologies, including “Cookies,” local browser storage, and “Web Beacons.” A “Cookie” is a small amount of data a website operator, or a third party whose content is embedded in that website, may store in your web browser and that the website operator or, as applicable, the third party, can access when you visit the website. A Cookie may also refer to web-browser-based storage provided by Adobe’s Flash plugin (a “Flash Cookie”). The Service’s Cookies may contain user preferences, unique identifiers, and other non-Personal Information. A “Web Beacon” is a small, usually-transparent image placed on a web page that allows the operator of that image, which may be the operator of the website you visit or a third party, to read or write a Cookie.

Your operating system and web browser may allow you to erase information stored in Cookies, Flash Cookies, and local browser storage. But if you do so, you may be forced to login to the Services again and you may lose some preferences or settings. You may also be able to set your browser to refuse all website storage or to indicate when it is permitted, but some features of our Services may not function properly without it We may use Cookies to keep you logged in, save your preferences for the Services, and to collect information about how you use our Services. 

More information about managing Cookies is available [here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). Cookie management tools provided by your browser may not affect Flash Cookies. More information about managing Flash Cookies is available here. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for your local browser storage, please refer to the end user documentation for your browser. 

To help us collect this information, we use third-party software and services like Google Analytics. Google Analytics’ collection and use of non-Personal Information is subject to its own privacy policy, which you can read [here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

## Transparency and Choice; Do Not Track Signals

You may request access to your Personal Information by sending an email to [support@file.io](mailto:support@file.io). We will try to locate and provide you with your Personal Information and give you the opportunity to correct this data, if it is inaccurate, or to delete it, at your request. But, in either case, we may need to retain it for legal reasons or for legitimate business purposes. You may also remove any content that you post to the Services using the deletion or removal options within the Service. However, we (and you) are not able to control information that you have already shared with other users or made available to third parties through the Services. 

If you need further assistance with removing any content you posted through the Services, you can email us at support@file.io. Removal of your posted content may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal from our computer systems. 

We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected, or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, would be extremely impractical, or relate to information that is not associated with your Personal Information. In any case, where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. 

Please be aware thatif you request us to delete your Personal Information, you may not be able to continue to use your subscription to the Services. Also, even if you request that we delete your Personal Information, we may need to retain certain information for a limited period of time to satisfy our legal, audit and/or dispute resolution requirements.

We support the development and implementation of a standard "do not track" browser feature that provides customers with control over the collection and use of information about their web-browsing activities. Once a standardized "do not track" feature is released, we intend to adhere to the browser settings accordingly. 

You can opt out of receiving marketing e-mails from us by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in the e-mails. Please note that it may take up to ten (10) business days for your opt-out request to be processed. Also, even if you opt out of marketing e-mails, we may continue to send you certain account-related e-mails, such as notices about your account and confirmations of transactions you have requested. 

## Children

The Services are not intended for users under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from users under 13 years of age. We do not authorize users under 13 years of age to use the Services. 

## Information Security

We utilize reasonable information security measures to safeguard your Personal Information against unauthorized access, modification, or destruction. For example, we utilize Secure Socket Layer (SSL), Transport Layer Security (TLS), or similar encryption technology when sensitive data is transmitted over the Internet, and use firewalls to help prevent external access into our network. However, no data transmission over the Internet and no method of data storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its security.

We restrict access to Personal Information to our employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, improve or support our Services. 

## Your California Privacy Rights

A California resident who has provided Personal Information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (“California Customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed Personal Information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of Personal Information, upon receipt of a request by a California Customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of Personal Information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing a customer’s Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for direct marketing purposes and providing a cost free means to exercise that right. To prevent disclosure of your Personal Information for use in direct marketing by a third party for its own purposes, do not opt in to or authorize such use when you provide Personal Information through the Services. Please note that whenever you allow your Personal Information to be shared with a third party to communicate with you, your information will be subject to that third party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California Customers may request further information about our compliance with California’s privacy law by e-mailing support@file.io.Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.

## Third Party Websites. 

Please note that the Services may link or integrate with third-party sites, services or apps. We are not responsible for the privacy or security policies or practices or the content of such third parties. Accordingly, we encourage you to review the privacy and security policies and terms of service of those third parties so that you understand how those websites collect, use, share and protect your information.

## Changes to this Policy

We may modify or update this Privacy Policy periodically with or without prior notice by posting the updated policy on this page. You can always check the “Last Updated” date at the top of this document to see when the Privacy Policy was last changed. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by reasonable means, which may be by e-mail or posting a notice of the changes on our website prior to the changes becoming effective. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST STOP USING THE SERVICES AFTER THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF SUCH CHANGES (WHICH IS THE “LAST UPDATED” DATE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY). 

## Questions

To ask questions about our Privacy Policy or to lodge a complaint, contact us at: 

humbly, LLC  
P.O. Box 15004  
Philadelphia, PA 19130  
Email: support@file.io
